so let's talk about the Right View
then like
um how would you describe it how would
you describe it right view view
um
knowledge of
knowledge of absence of suffering that
is
not that's not your knowledge but that's
just that's not something that you
create that's there because you uh want
this or because you kind of created
is it's basically knowledge of how the
mind is how the body is how the
Aggregates are in and of
themselves that leaves no room
for uh for great aversion or
delusion is there any other way that you
could describe it CU that can be taken
by anybody there's
nothing there's nothing in the
description you provided that could not
be
assimilated what do you mean assimilated
assimilated by somebody who is also says
like yeah of course I know what the body
is what the mind is I know the gion
origin but still they
not so is there another way to convey
the Right View that a puug would not be
able to relate to it so easily and
appropriate it so quickly anyone
quickly anyone
well there's that description that goes
along the lines of no no I mean your
description well when you see for
yourself what is for your harm and
others harm and what is for your benefit
and others benefit and well not for
others harm but like yeah so see that
harm but like yeah so see that
connection between
the way you live your life and the
result of that not just that's good and
that's bad again yeah that's not wrong
but same it's on the same level
like yeah anybody with with like basic
amount of information can say yeah of
course I know how my actions lead to my
welfare or
not any anything more
acute yeah CU it's like what you you
speaking about he knows what is a waste
of time and what is not a waste of time
time yeah but then anybody can
assimilate that so basically all these
are descriptions of the result of the
Right View and it's like what is the
Right View that somebody without the right you
View that somebody without the right you
kind just oh yeah of course then I'll
just assimilate that because can kind of
reason my way around
it as as she started again or what what
nand said as well both are correct
but as I said even somebody without a
Right View can easily assimilate the
same description and say yeah of course
oh thus I have a right view now cuz I
understand that so it has to be
something more acute in terms of descri
view that pu cannot assimilate because
it would go over his
head so yeah I'm asking for some
examples of
that the inability to be moved by
whatever appears basically or you experience the
appears basically or you experience the
inability to take it personally so to
but then
again whatever is whatever thing is is
there and you can say it even like um
so there's
uh there's greed there's aversion
there's delusion there's like your or
emotion or feelings or pressures MH
and the thing is that if these if
whatever is whatever is a thing is seen
as a thing including a feeling or
something that's like pressuring you but
if it's if if it's actually just seen
for what it
is the thing is
that it can't um anything that's like
that could be called greed or that could
be called a ver or could be called like
anger or whatever
um whatever creates suffering whatever
is UNH wholesome whatever can make a
person um do bad things whatever is
um none of that can be there none of
that none of that none of that can be
there when any um into any feeling or
any pressure whenever that's seen for
itself it just there's no room for those
things but it's not because
because
you I think the important thing is it's
not you getting rid of it it's not you
knowing how to see a thing as a thing
knowing how to see a thing as a thing so
that there is no room for the for
the this kind of any gratuitous anxiety
any any fear absence of fear like zero
fear basically where there's no room for
it but not because you got rid of us or
you did something to us but just the
knowledge of how it cannot be there and
it's so it's like not only and and the
thing is it's also not about just being
able to like experience that absence of
sense of Freedom once or kind of having
a sense of it but actually knowing where
it came from what led to it what made it
possible and and so not just kind of
randomly being able to I don't know make
your mind calm or you can make your mind
genuinely Cal or free or have like a
sense of complete Freedom mm but that
doesn't constitute the Right View it's
more it's it's knowledge
of how that comes
about can you be more
specific cuz I can just now read this
eful path and everything else and essays
on it and say that's how it comes about
and it's fact correct that's about it's
correct but that wouldn't
be no but I'm I know it wouldn't be but
I'm saying is when you say knowledge of
how it comes about again it's something
can relate because he might be have been
studying the sutas a lot so yeah go go
ahead then give me a more specific
example of how that
knowledge comes
about you said it's it's not the you do
something on account of these things
it's how you see them yes so how you see
them how do you see them that's what
you're asking describe the right VI how
do you see them cuz yes exactly it's and
see that's already something that pan
will have harder time assimilating
quickly because he's used to doing stuff
yes he's used to managing things he's
used to countering things is used to um
you know spending time in concentration
so that the mind then is calm so that
then I'm not bothered and all these
things but if you say oh it's none of
that it's completely the opposite
direction of that it's not what you're
doing and it's certainly not that you
have to do something it's more like
simply the way you see things MH but now
that can be mystified and he say oh
seeing the way things are and it's just
Oneness and eess and so on so you have
to be more specific so then how do you
see things that
instantaneously doesn't even free from
Fear it's simply there is no room there
is no room for fear even if you want to
be afraid there is no room for fear to
to be there yeah and I think fear is how
see fear is a specific one like or an
anxiety let's say fear anxiety Dua but
they're the yeah um
the way so it's not on the level of like
describing the thing but describing how
to see it yeah well how it SE how SE
either way as as risen as
manifested but that's again something
you can it doesn't yeah like it's the
right viewing the right viewing yeah the
right view is the right viewing yeah so
the the way you see it the way
you the right view is a way of seeing
things uh
detached yeah that's that's all correct
but the actual seeing of it describe
that not what comes as a result of
seeing and then yeah so right it's not
even about like cuz even seeing it's
like oh well I'm seeing that I'm and
thing is has to be some word used so I
just use that cuz you said it but uh you
can use word attending which is more
corre it's the way attend it you're not
it's the way attend it you're not
looking at it necessarily in that sense
I mean you could
describe uh yeah of course which so
describe then
Yara in ways relevant to fear or duka
that you just brought up that Dan would
not be able to relate to because he's
used to managing his duka and
fear so how can you then attend an
Arisen thing so that there is no room
for that thing to exhibit pressure or
any form of daoka on
you so describe that way of attending for
so take the experience of anxiety or
fear and describe to me how you would be
attending to
it well you know you say tending to the
situation as a whole you know Det
attached from what you know the fear at
the same time simultaneously
seeing the body there so you everything
you you you're cutting up things things
are detached cut
apart you know like that simil of the
The Butcher and the
cow yeah yeah so things are like
that but I want it more acutely so
without resorting to oh you can do this
or you can do that you have have the
experience of frightening experience or
anxiety just in relation to
that how can you attend to
it that would result
in there being no room for any
discomfort besides saying not that's not
myself well besides besides that not
myself is the result of
but it's uh yeah once you know how to
write end it you can keep reminding
yourself with not for me not mine not
myself as would encourage it but I want
it just acutely on the way of seeing it
as it is right there seeing through it
that again you don't have to do anything
else that's why it's liberating that's
why amidst suffering s it doesn't suffer
it's a nature
of all of that's
correct but none of that is the acute
again yeah ceasing nature it's on the
level of the Insight because you
attended to it
rightly what is that attending to the
rightly that's what I want it
described well in a way not putting
yourself in relation to it or not trying
to see it or overly Define it or
just in way not putting things where you
want them to be or in a way you want
them to be or you do in a way you don't
want them to be
in way seeing them you can only do that
because so your ability to
attend is second to it being there
second in in a kind of a sitting on top
of this it's not like you you're not not
able to like choose to attend to is it
precedes the the fact that you're
already attending to us yeah and that
that's and it's that like kind of
already thess so that is kind of the
thing that you need to
attend attend without attending it yeah
so it's like not attending it but
recognizing it as kind of already
underneath the attention yeah and and
then that's it's that element basically
that is impossible to appropriate or
impossible to own impossible like even
if you you want even if you even if you
turn all of your attention to it to try
to try to make it yours try to you know
you can't because because it's just it's
impossible it's undermined it's
completely under always remains out of
the reach basically it's completely out
and like you know even if you know even
if you doubt it with all your mind even
if nothing it's completely inaccessible
and it's inaccessible because that's
that's literally just how it is yeah and
it's so it's under exactly like it it
undermines it's undermined already or it
undermines itself as you put it and
that's there's no room there's just it's
impossible for there to be anxiety it's
just not there's there's no there's no
basis for it and it's
not it it's it's not like
um oh I just I'm not moved by this or
whatever there's just there's no
possibility no basis for for anxiety or
yeah there's no possibility of being
moved by yeah and that's that's exactly
no that's it see that's that cannot be
appropriated so
easily um and it all bows down to that
like a person General everyone is used
to attending to things and he puts that
first they put that first so the fact
that you're already attending to dealing
with your anxiety or
fear means it has arisen already it's
been enduring there underneath so to
speak it presented itself you find it
there through your
attention um but the weight the emphasis
is on your attention so although it came
second so to speak structurally not
necessarily Tempo temp
temporarily uh you put that first so
your attention and dealing with it is
the center of the experience expence
failing to understand that all of your
efforts all of your movements all of
your concerns all of your Cravings all
of your reactions actions and
counteractions and so on are because the
thing is still there
enduring so that's why sensory strain
has to come first so you stop acting out
in those grossly outward ways um and
then internally you still might be
moving and the mind still might be
jumping at the prospects of dealing with
it and doing this encountering it
but through all of that through saying
yes no both yes and no neither yes nor
no if you don't act out and if you are
making some effort to discern what else
is simultaneously there you'll find it's
there is a thing that is simultaneously
there with you attending to it and that
thing comes first not your
attention and then yeah then there is no
room for anything there nothing else
it's with this this is the P
principal that's why whoever sees the D
sees P whoever sees P sees the D in
other words soana begins to
see um and yeah that's that's why it's like
um and yeah that's that's why it's like
um it's instantaneous that's why it's
aala it's Timeless because there is no
time involved between you attending to
this and that thing being
given and that's why it's not a matter
of like
um then yeah then it becomes Timeless as
in it is not it's not a matter
of doing some other unrelated or sort of
semi- related things more like literally
just practicing or uh developing that
developing that same that simultaneous
recognition further and further and
preventing yourself from engaging with
it in these
U manners that would put your attention
first mhm so by that I mean not distracting
mhm so by that I mean not distracting
yourself like because there will still
be um in soop's experience there would
still be
aspects of his life
that are still putting his attention
first as opposed to the the the
experience he's attending such as
sensuality ill will hindrances and so on
and that's how you purify mind from it
but it does have the principle the
principle being how do I free myself
from this hindrance or from that issue
or this issue by seeing through it not
by doing this or
that and um and yeah that's that's why
it's like directly visible Here and Now
not involving
time for as long as there are five
Aggregates there is the possibility of
seeing through them correctly
and that is that's an important point
that
um like that's the direct that's another
way of describing the direct
relationship or relevance of um virtue
and sense restraint as
in because if you haven't been
developing virtue haven't been
developing sens it doesn't matter what
language or how much you try to wrap
your head around this kind of
notion your whole
yeah your whole mindset is just about me
controlling things me doing things me
being that's we say often enduring
things on the right level so if you have
not oh he said something and he's
completely wrong and although I know I'm
upset and I shouldn't say anything while
I'm upset I'll still say it because it's
for greater good it's for the benefit of
everybody I must point out their mistake
you feel externally Justified internally
you acted out of pressure of ill will or
irritation or whatever which means for
as long as you're not able to endure
those things rightly internally for as
long as it takes regardless of what kind
of Injustice you're looking at and so on
uh means you haven't endured things
sufficiently enough and that means
basically uh you refuse by by refusing
to endure it sufficiently enough you
refuse to put your attention of the
issue second like even if you keep saying to
second like even if you keep saying to
yourself I'm not I'm attending through
this and I'm seeing through it and I'm
not giving it Priority you you do simply
by acting out by not being able to
endure that's how you you um you
actually already pervert your order you
already put your attention first as
while it should be
second and that's also why it's
a it's impossible
to build up any sense of uh
this is another thing I was thinking
about build up any sense of conceit for
example on the right practice like
because people do that with any other
kind of spiritual practice I feel better
and you you might be factually kind of
developing developing some things that
genuinely sort of make you more um
virtuous but more able to manage things
but less suffer less than other people
and so on um you can't be conce and even
like even if you come across as whatever
extremely confident or blunt or rude
that's not the measure of conceit if if
people think that's conceited it's
because usually they themselves cannot
understand um Behavior they could be
like that but it's not effectively
conceited because if they were to behave
that way it would be conceeded so it's a
kind of fallacy that they project um and
it's that whole kind of understanding
that's that's implied when you when you
discern how to attend things rightly in
a way of not attending
them attending that which is there
without attending
it um then yeah no no room for UNH
wholesome no room for vanity for conceit
for sensuality U no room for
sensuality U no room for
hindrances for
meta you
any other way we can
describe attending to things without
attending
them like how can you attend things
without attending
them isn't there a
contradiction well like you said it's
about where you put the emphasis so
recognizing that to be able to attend to
something it has to be there so
presented what
does how can you say it differently has
to be there how can that be
described given beforehand given
beforehand yeah so what is given
beforehand has to be there what do those things
has to be there what do those things
have in common you don't have they're
known they're known exactly I was going
to say how do you know that cuz you know
that know you know and that's and that's
not you're doing exactly and that's
actually nearly a way if you can ask
what do what do I know as in what's what
can I not help but no but no and that's
actually even even the meaning of the
word knowledge yeah that's that's
literally just what it means what's
given there absolutely yeah
for Consciousness yeah but conscious off but
Consciousness yeah but conscious off but
again like uh it's sort
of it's been proliferated so much that
people when they talk about
Consciousness it's not nowhere near the
Consciousness so you have to kind of
find a practical basis such as whatever
experience of fear or this or that as we
did and then talk about attention and
then talk about okay but so you the fact
that you're attending it the fact that
you're dealing with it means it's it's
given beforehand it was Arisen there on
its own it came first so to speak not
before M it's at the same time but it's
under you let's say it like that and
it's like oh but you do already know
that which is why you're choosing to
attend to it in this manner or that
manner trying to get rid of it trying to
do this trying to do that CU it's
already known to that extent yes sure
you don't understand it
because if you did you wouldn't be
trying to act out of
it you would then emphasize the
knowledge of it being there beforehand
while it's exerting pressure on you and
refrain from acting out of that pressure
which would tip the the the scales back
onto that perverted
order and that's kind of probably I
think the most acutely that you could
describe how to get the right view for
somebody who doesn't have the right
view when faced with daoka big or small
doesn't matter by not acting out of it you
matter by not acting out of it you
discern that it's given beforehand while
you're not acting out of it for as long
as it takes forever you're ready to do
it forever to emphasize the
discernment of what you already
know at the expense of acting out of it
and telling to yourself that it came
there beforehand and everything else
because you really want to get rid of it
and that's the the subtle
trap that Pan's mind would be falling
into so this is perfectly intelligible
you can understand this but then when
you're actually under the pressure of
some form of
daoka your first emphasis
is attend to it through the attitude of
wanting it to go away wanting to get rid
of it and now you do what ainol said all
right so it's there beforehand given I
know that see none of that is actually
correct now so first and foremost is I mustn't
now so first and foremost is I mustn't
do anything including what said you must
do so then what you're left with you get
to discern as being there and then don't
act out of
it and rinse and
repeat and if you're keeping the
precepts and Cate you want to need you
you wouldn't need to be seeking daoka
for your practice there will be
plenty plenty pressures to go
around what other way can use to
describe
it so you can know
it without well you can attend it
without attending it in the ways
of you used to uh you can know it as
being given
beforehand again without attending it
directly you recognize that it's there
on its
own what other
ways what are the description of that
relationship between you and that thing
between you and a and
D how can we describe it they would not
involve time they would not require
doing what are the properties own terms
on terms it's yeah again what's the
what's the
property of that experience the whole
few experiencing pressure of anxiety to
act out of
it so you have the Oris phenomenon of
pressure discomfort you're not acting
out of it so what's
the what are the characteristics of that
experience you under that pressure that
has a reason its own and so on and so
for
was like the main characteristics they
would prevent you from putting yourself first
prevent you from putting yourself first
and trying to deal with it even if you
want to even if your mind is still
revolving around those thoughts rightly
established attitude of
what would
disable any
effectiveness of the mental Tendencies
to put yourself first and deal with the
discomfort or engage with
Comfort if viewed
rightly what would be the most
impersonal characteristic of the right
viewing that's what I come with that
it's impersonal yeah but what makes it
impersonal what makes it impermanent
impermanent
it's no no hold on you're drifting away
now we're just listing things so we're
we're talking about
your experience being under the pressure
of a reisen
phenomenon so it's like me dealing with
this or not dealing with this attending
it or not both neither what do I do move
left right up down away evade indulge
give up so there is that relationship
between you and that
thing so what is
the main core characteristic of that
relationship that is is why thing is
impermanent that is why the thing is
unable that is why if you're viewing it
through that characteristic of that
relationship you would be
unable to put yourself first so you're
talking about this Rel like as in you
you there's you and this yeah there is
you and there is the pressure that's why
you put yourself first and what you want
first kind of so you're talking about
how to
then I'm talking about right viewing of
that relationship Rel so that it what is
its core characteristic of that right
viewing I would say kind of being
complete in and of itself as in there's
has having no um
here you go like that's that's the
entirety of it it's the enti of it that
there isn't when when when you have two
things mhm that are complete to each other
mhm that are complete to each other
extent how do they relate what is their
relationship then how would you call it
simultaneous exactly simultane okay and
that's the point the simultaneity of it
see even if somebody without a Right
View were to start training
simultaneously knowing what they're
attending while they're attending it it
would bring them closer to the knowledge
of that thing without needing to attend
it
directly cuz simultaneity of you and
that thing is not something you can do
doesn't matter how much you
emphasize your attending and your
dealing and your movement and your
reaction or whatever else it remains
unchanged it's all within
that so with this this is and for as
long that remains unchanged
in that simultaneously is there and then
you realize once you recognize that
simultaneity that's why you cannot own
things because your ownership comes
second to it it's just one of the things
one of the one of the two things that
are simultaneously dependent on each
other to the extent that they are or
trying to own or trying to possess or
trying to control or acting upon putting
yourself first in regard to things that
are simultaneously
present it's the reason fora that's why
why they're impermanent CU they are
otherwise yeah and and that's also
because if you see that that's
simultaneous and the dependency of it
that you can't
have the sense of like if you if it's
the sense of me for example and this
other thing no you have as in that but what
thing no you have as in that but what
yeah you have that you start with that
but you you see them as
simultaneously dependent I me they like
it's literally kind of that's what I
meant when there I know that's why I
said go on carry on because that brings
you closer to the point when there are
two and there is no other option there
there's neither can be the one one
exactly and that's the point and that's
why you do start with your sense of self
you don't deny it but by seeing it
simultaneously dependent on something
else that's not your sense of self right
there to the same extent it will cease
to be yours it will still
remain depend from Still Remains in the
nand what does not remain there is the
ownership of either or both and so on so
exactly the on the level of the
experience as a whole not like me in
this chair or something although if
you're viewing it rightly it can be
anything but in the beginning you need
to start seeing it on the level of your
experience as a whole like your totality
of your experience Here and Now seated
in this room sense of I am with and then
whatever whatever wherever your
attention lands whether it's a
particular feeling or a thought or a
memory or or or a pleasure or pain
doesn't matter anything that you are
relating to there and then to that
extent and if you start seeing it as
simultaneously enduring as opposed to me
dealing with this then me dealing with
that no it's me dealing with this while
both are there to the same
extent oh a new me dealing with this
with something new to the same extent
then a new me dealing with something
something new to the same extent cuz
that's what really
is and it's the recognition of that
simultaneity that can bring you the
closest to the right
View and it's not something you can do
you cannot possibly lay out a method of
Step by Step method of the one two three
and then you see the
simultaneity and that is pretty much the
core of the the beginning that remains
unchanged from the start till the end
till the completion of the
practice so the point is get rid of yeah
so the point is
like do with this disease yeah exactly
because the actual principle regardless
of its formulation the suas always
starts with this this
is
must that's it every single time then it
can sometimes be eight factors or 12
factors or 16 factors and so on but you
realize the princi remains
unchanged so you can't have the
exemplification of the principle
contradicting the principle because then
it's not the exemplification of the
principle so if the principle is with
this this is then the exemplification of
it has to be within that principle is
just basic logic um but again given the
whole commentarial tradition and Abid
dama and the whole amount of of
proliferated misleading information
created on top of it
now when people hear dependent
origination they have those those those
Wheel of Life uh tanas and and stuff in
their mind of how you know from rebirth
protest and stuff like that fully
ignoring or being completely unaware uh
of the
principle so put the whole dependent
origination aside as a
formulation and just talk about
Yar which is already the principle of P
when seen rightly and so
develops learns how to attend to things
simultaneously without attending to them
directly we'll then see how but
formulation describes their very thing
but it's highly likely you would arrive
at that thing through studying ptit and
formulation today because of everything
that happen in between with commentarial
and stud studies and everything else
piles and piles and piles of pretty much
misleading directions is that that Su
says whether the Buddha gives us that
basic description do you see this
exactly yeah imag do you see this as its
condition Y and then he ask the monks
the one who attends like this can he
doubt that says no impossible the one
who doesn't attend to it like this can
doubt arise
yes that's like the most it's as acute
as he gets
yeah do you see this do you see this as
its condition do you see the sensation
of this this condition uh yeah if this
is not would this be yeah
yeah two is there un isn't is there
uncertainty when there's doubt in regard
to this yes it's kind of a
so take your sense of self how however
you might be
feeling in its entirety here and now and
then discern without a abandoning
without attending something
else discern within that acute concrete
living sense of self that you are
discern that
something in its
core that that self depends
upon that it's not in your control
control
so bring that thing up to be
simultaneously there as an undermining
condition for your sense of self so and
then let it endure and it's going to the
mind will turn away from it and then you
repeat it and then you repeat it and
then you repeat
it and those same things that's why and
you you should be feeling it yeah it's
not just on the level of like so okay if
you get your sense of self feeling this
or that right here right now and while
that's present discern something in its
heart that undermines it yet it's not in
your control cannot be possessed without
abandoning this sense of self here and
now you you possess it when you make it
a new thing when you attend to it
becomes your sense of self but now
you've fallen from that simultaneous
recognition so you're just moving from
one to the other from one to the other
maintaining your sense of ownership
because you're not undermining things
through that simultaneity
so that's why it's important to
recognize and not just attend to what oh
that's a nature that's a that's a nature
no no no take your sense of self however
it feels with its safety with its
ownership with its
implications and without thinking about
something else discern even if it's a
vague thing that there must be
something simultaneously present that
actually your entirety of this
experience of sense of self depends
yet that thing cannot be yours at the
same time it can be yours after but then
time it can be yours after but then
something else won't be yours at the
same time so you're always undermined
whatever your attention rests something
else will undermine it but you could
start yeah with just what makes you uh
deeply anxious this sort of deep
existential anxiety that everybody
experiences and see what is and the B
what is that on the basis of that first
first you you you would have to start
with exens anxiety and then first you
would have to not put yourself first as
somebody's trying to get rid of it so
first there's exential anxiety okay now
let me not try to get rid of it mhm so
see so the exential anxiety is there the
sense of self is there
yeah let it endure keep it keep it
maintain it simultaneously
recognized and so then like that's
why I think you could say like the same
contemplations that
would without the Right View be the
source of the deepest fear or anxiety
would become the most Pleasant thing to
think about really because that and
bring you the closest to the right view
because it is the measure then of
ation yeah there was actually that other
Su it's something similar to that I I
think it may be said
um it would not be if it were not it
would not would not be for me it will
not be and it will not be mine it won't
be for it won't be mine and and so he
says this is um terrifying to an
ordinary person yeah and to an an arant
or somebody or where the Liberation is
it is where the Liberation is yes and
it's terrifying not because it's
genuinely terrifying in
itself the sensation is not terrifying
it's terrifying only if you still are
unknowingly putting yourself first which
means your sense of ownership and
control is there maintained and that's
why this is the the utmost yeah
contradiction to it challenge to it and
that's why it's the most frightening one
so if you have that like you know most
people wouldn't be able to hold it at
the same time without losing perspective
without being overwhelmed by the fear or
anxiety if it's on that level but you
can work up to it and you work up to it
by with what I just described so you
start by
recognizing I'm here to this extent such
and such my sense of self sense of I am
real as such no issue with it and with
that experience as a whole within that
experience as a whole without again
trying to attend to a new thing or fall
into like a linear psychological
explanation discern well even just take
your your body present here your Beating
Heart even the Arisen feeling for that
matter that pretty much defines your
sense of self there and then you realize
you had no say in its simultaneous
presence there you have no say in the
simultaneous presence of the Beating
Heart here yet my whole life depends on
it this whole sense of self depends on
this I mean living heart right here as
I'm thinking this if that changes the
slightest obstruction or something none
of this can remain
what do you do next repeat
it and if it's if you haven't forgotten
it if you haven't overly attended to it
and made it into a new thing then just
just let it endure there and obviously
you're going to feel it and that's the
measure when you're right
attending kind of first makes you feel
things more but then makes you unfe them
same thing you're not doing anything
extra just through repeatedly attending
them the feelings were increasing the
fear the pressure you didn't back down
you kept repeatedly attending to it
rightly concurrently you only it
indirectly whichever way you want to
translate it and now those feelings are
being unfelt while nothing has nothing has
unfelt while nothing has nothing has
changed well what is changing is the the
shift of the emphasis from over here me
I am onto not mine not I am over there
it still remains that which was self
remain is just not yours anymore